Seeno, Gargal Channel, Go Go!
Today's project is an Uber exchange.
This time, the three of us are going to exchange Uber rides, for example, I'll ask Kira-chan and Kira-chan will ask Momo-ga.
How do you feel about this?
It was a one-day exchange, but it was morning, noon, and night.
I could really see her personality.
It was so luxurious!
I was like, "What's this girl? I want her for myself.
You had a lesson on that day this time?
Yes, and it wasn't all the same person, so I was able to go at random.
Please take a look at the video to see how it went and what kind of products I received.
So, first of all, I ordered breakfast for Kira-chan... well, I already did, but I ordered a white mocha, a sandwich, and waffles from Suttava.
I don't know...
I thought it would be better to order Starbucks, so I decided to go with that.
I'll wait for the arrival... I'd like to send my breakfast to Claire's...
I'd like to send breakfast to Claire's, so I'll start looking for it right away!
I don't think Claire eats much for breakfast.
I don't know... a sandwich or something.
A sandwich would be nice.
A sandwich... a little fancy... so she can enjoy it in the morning.
Looks good?
But... Claire doesn't like vegetables.
Oh well.
Claire likes Coke.
I'll send her an egg sandwich and a Coca-Cola.
I'm going to order breakfast for Momoka today.
So, today Momoka sent me a food that she doesn't like
She can't eat corn, beans, blueberries, raspberries, raisins, and cinnamon.
I'm not going to send her these foods.
Well, Momoka, what would you like for breakfast?
But I don't know how much Momoka eats in the morning.
Maybe I'd like to give her pancakes... a little bit oshan-nee in the morning...
I wonder what Momoka usually eats for breakfast.
Is she a big eater or a small eater?
Ah! There's St. Mark's.
St. Mark's is good, isn't it?
Pancakes! Wait a minute!
Claire brought breakfast while I was ordering Momoka's rice!
I'm so happy! What's in it?
What's in the bag?
Too mean!
But, pancake set... pancake... they have pancake set.
That's good, isn't it?
Mac's pancake set.
Big Breakfast Deluxe.
Pancakes...
It's got a lot of stuff on it.
Yes, I ordered it.
Yes, that's right...
Breakfast from Momoka
Delivered!
It looks like this.
What kind of box is this?
and
It's breakfast.
Every day...
Coke arrives in the mail.
Oh, my God!
Oh, wow!
Looks delicious!
Egg sandwich!
Ta-da! Egg sandwich!
Egg sandwich.
And fries too!
But there's one thing that happened...
They gave me a Coke, too.
But I don't have a washing machine.
I don't have a washing machine.
Unfortunately...
I can't drink it now.
Hmmm...
Is there any way to open it? I mean, there's no line.
I can't. I can't do it with my fingernails.
Well, I'll just... I'll just take my time.
I'll have a drink at some point.
Why did he give me the Coke?
Bon appétit.
Mmm-hmm.
A sandwich like this.
Here you go.
Yum! Delicious!Yum! Delicious!
Bread is delicious in the morning, isn't it?
What did everyone order?
I wondered what Momoko's rice would be like.
I'm glad it was so ordinary.
This house is a front door.
It's like, "What kind of small house do you live in?
It's such a small house.
So breakfast arrived from Kira to me!
Dororororororororororororororororororororororororororororor
McDonald's.
It's nice!
Isn't it too much? So much!
That's a lot.
What? What's this?
What is this? Does it look like caramel?
Huh!
Oh, my God.
What? McDonald's has these.
It's a muffin.
With meat.
Wow.
It's evolved.
Oh, my goodness.
That's a gorgeous breakfast.
I'm a little...
I'm not used to talking on my own.
I sound like a Gifu.
Oh...
Hello?
Hello! It's arrived!
Oh, thank goodness!
Oh, he's so happy... McDonald's... they have those... eggs in them...
I really wanted to give her pancakes, but the moment I found them...
I really wanted to give you pancakes, but the moment I found them, I thought... this is the best!
I could drink a caramel latte.
What's a caramel latte?
I'll have one now.
I'm going to have one now.
I'll drink it now!
You don't know how much Momochan usually eats in the morning, do you?
Oh, that's true.
That's why I was wondering.
I'm glad you're happy.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
See you later.
Bon appétit!
Usually...
I eat in the dining room.
But I'm a little embarrassed to talk about it in front of my family.
I'm eating alone under the bed.
Under the bed.
But there's plenty of room.
It's morning.
I could put this meat on a muffin.
Maybe I should put an egg in there too?
Maybe.
Because it's a McDonald's.
It looks like a McDonald's.
That's more like it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is this what it looks like?
I don't know... this might sound really weird... but...
I'm thinking pancakes, scrambled eggs and bacon for breakfast.
That's crazy.
What do you guys eat for breakfast?
Oh, but you know, we used to eat a lot of cereal too.
Like in elementary school.
Oh, but this one doesn't come off at all.
Seriously, it doesn't come off.
I guess I'm not supposed to eat it.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so good!It's so good!
I really wanted to drink a Starbucks when I saw it earlier.
Now for my breakfast.
Huh!
Wait, what's this?
White mocha!
What?
What is it?
What? Aren't you happy? Breakfast like this
American waffles.
Oh, here it is! Hirona Ham & Mario! It's so good!
Isn't it too much for breakfast? But I'm happy.
Oh, and I fell.
And you chose white mocha. You really know what you're doing.
I love white mocha.
Yum! Delicious! It's so good!
Which should I eat first?
I want a waffle, too, so I guess I should just eat them both.
I'll have this one.
Oh, wait, maybe I want a waffle.
But I want this one too!
We can have both.
Yummy!
Yum!
Bon appétit!
I'm so happy.
Yeah, it's so good!
I hope it's edible.
I got it!
I'll call him.
Hello?
Thank you so much.
That's great.
The video's rolling now.
Oh, it is?
Thank you very much.
Can I eat?
I can eat it.
Hey, Ken-chan...
Ken-chan was a customer?
I didn't know.
I put syrup in it.
He's a genius for choosing white mocha.
You really know what you're doing.
That's great.
They're here.
Enjoy your lunch.
Okay, I will.
Bye-bye.
I just ordered lunch for Momoka.
It's from a place called Soup Stock.
It's some kind of soup called Borscht with rice and oolong tea.
and oolong tea.
Um...
Momoka asked for something other than
Momoka asked for something other than McDonald's, so I made it a little different from McDonald's.
So I tried to make it a little different from a Mac.
I made it a little bit different from MacDonald's.
Now I'm waiting for the arrival!
Okay, so...
I'm going to choose lunch for Kira now.
I'd like to choose a lunch for Kira.
I'm not sure what to choose.
Kira said she doesn't like tomatoes.
So I thought I'd try to choose something without tomatoes.
I was just looking at the kebabs.
I can't really tell from the picture.
But you seem to like kebabs.
I was a little sad if it was just kebabs.
I'd like to send you some cucumbers, which I like.
Do you like cucumbers?
I hope so.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
Okay, so it's lunchtime.
It's lunchtime.
I'm going to order lunch for Claire.
I'd like to order lunch from Claire.
I like Claire's ramen or something like that.I like Claire Ramen and stuff.
I was thinking I could have some ramen.
But it depends on what you ate this morning.
What did I eat this morning?
I'm a little... I'm not a lunch person.
Nan! Nan.
I think I'll send some Nan.
I don't think I've had naan
I don't think I've eaten it.
I know you like Claire.
I think Claire likes naan, too.
This curry is definitely Butter Chicken Curry.
I'd like to use cheese naan instead of regular naan.
I'd like to try cheese naan.
I'm going to put some meaningless ebizen in it.
I'm going to put some meaningless shrimp cakes in it.
Is that okay?
I'd like to send naan to Claire.
I'd like to send Nan to Claire.
Yes, so, I've just received
Lunch has arrived.
I'm going to open it.
There's something I'm really curious about.
This one.
What do you think it is?
I don't know what it is either.
I don't know.
It looks like a candy.
I think it's some kind of deep-fried candy.
I think.
I don't know when I should eat it.
I'll leave it for now.
So...
Look, look... what a surprise!
It's curry.
Yay! I like it.
And Kira and I often go out to eat at a restaurant together, so I guess she picked it for me.
I'm going to eat it now. Bon appétit.
Looks delicious! Is it butter chicken?
It's good.
And it tastes like cheese.
Look, cheese.
Go ahead.
Hot.
Look, it's so cheesy.
It's delicious.
We always have cheese naan no matter what we eat.
We always have cheese naan when we go out to eat.
But once I had the cheese naan, I couldn't eat the regular naan anymore.
But after I had the cheese naan, I couldn't eat the regular naan anymore.
So I chose the cheese naan.
I'm curious about this one.
Maybe I'll try one...
What's this?
Is this in a curry shop like that?
I've never seen one like this.
I've never seen it before.
Yes, I have.
I've had it before.
What does it taste like?
No.
I'm off today. I mean, I'm not off. I'm just going to do this.
I don't really have anything planned. I just need to be home to do this.
I've been watching on my phone at home.
So I'm going to ask someone for an Uber, and then I'm going to eat the Uber that comes for me.
I'm really happy.
I also want to call the person who ordered it.
I want to call the person who ordered me an Uber while I'm eating.
But I only have this phone, the one I'm using right now.
I don't know.
I don't hide it. After eating or before eating.
I'm enjoying the food.
Okay, so...
Lunch arrived from Claire!
Here we go!
This looks like soup, since we had McDonald's this morning. Let's have a look.
There are two soups in this package. Oh, I'm so happy!
Oh, wow! Soup. This is soup and this is rice.
Maybe it's beef stew. Maybe I should put lemon in it.
I wonder if I should put lemon in it.
Ham scissors work great.The ham scissors are doing a great job.
Mmm.
It's so delicious!
This is the best.
It's so luxurious!
But I haven't had it in a while.
I don't know.
It's like beef stew.
This is beef stew?
Yeah, it is.
Hmm? Wait, it says...
"Tokyo Borscht.
I wasn't sure.
But it's delicious.
Very good.
Yes, so...
Lunch arrived from Momoka!
I wonder what it is
What's in this plastic bag?
I'll open it.
What's this?
Kebab?
I'll open it.
There are two.
Here you go.
This is it.
Kebabs!
I'm so happy!
I love kebabs.
Ta-da!
Bon appétit.
Yay!
You haven't had kebabs in a while?
Bon appétit.
Yum! Delicious!
A little spicy.
Cheesy and delicious!
Yum! Yum!
What's this?
It's a little spicy.
It's so good!
Delicious! Thanks Momoka!
So, you know, I just got a line from her.
He said he'd like to order another one at a different store.
He said he's going to order one more besides this one.
I'm going to wait for it while I eat this.
Yes, I just received another one from Momoka.
What is it? This.
I don't get it.
What is it?
I paid 700 yen for this.
Isn't that bad?
Hey, 700 yen for a cucumber is not good!
Are you kidding me?
I called to say I got it.
I didn't get it, did I? Wait a minute.
Hello?
Um, cucumbers, what is it? What's this?
What do you mean?
I paid 700 yen for this cucumber.
What do you mean? Seriously.
Yes, yes, you mean the shipping cost?
Can I not spend money on this?
Well, I was expecting a little tapioca or something.
I was hoping for some tapioca or something, but...
With salt.
I see, it takes a little time.
Thank you very much.
And you're from Miyazaki Prefecture, so...
We have a member.
Thank you for the cucumbers from your hometown.
Please.
Excuse me.
Um, this girl was really calm.
I wonder...
But we've been given some, so we have to eat it.
Just a little.I'll just...
I'll eat.
Oh, is this the kind of thing you can eat raw?
I'll ask my mom.
Yes, I told my mom they can be eaten raw.
I'll eat it.
No way!
Bon appétit!
It's delicious!
I'm going to have this cooked for dinner or something.
Now the last one!
I'd like to order Momoka's dinner!
I had my mind made up.
I mean, there's one thing I've been thinking about.
There's something I've been thinking about.
Momoka asked for Korean food.
Korean food.
I think I'll look for Korean food.
I don't know, maybe one Korean food restaurant?
Korean food at least one?
I don't know, maybe one or two.
What kind of Korean food do you have in mind?
I don't know what kind of Korean food
I don't know.
I don't know what kind of Korean food you're thinking of, but there's a hot pot kind of place
I'm not sure what kind of Korean food it's supposed to be.
I think I'm going to go with chicken.
I think I'll have the yangnyeom chicken.
I'm going to have the yangnyeom chicken set meal.
Yes, sir.
Last of the Uber project!
I'm sending Kira for dinner.
I sent her Italian food.
Something like...
bread and roasted chicken thigh.
It's a bit of a night out, right?
I decided on something luxurious.
So now that it's nighttime
I'd like to deliver dinner to Claire now.
Okay?
I sent naan to Claire for lunch.
It's not bread-based.
I was thinking rice.
Oyakodon or something like that.
Wow, but this is the last time I'm sending it.
That was a lot of fun.
Claire likes beef tongue.
Negi-Shi Onigi-Shi Meat Kalbi Donburi!
Wow!
Eh, thick light tsukemen noodles.
Mm.
I also like noodles, so there's noodles too.
Eh, I'm so confused!
I have tapioca and
Hakata ramen and gyoza.
I delivered it to Claire as her dinner.
The dinner from Kira arrived, so
I'll open it.
Oh, it's ramen!
It says "ramen" on the outside!
Look.
Gyoza!
What kind of ramen is this?
Ramen!
I've been mixing and matching them all day.
I'm totally hungry.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious.
Ichiran?
It tastes like Ichiran.
It's not Ichiran, but of course...
Bon appétit.
Yes.
It's so good!
I haven't had tonkotsu ramen in a long time, so it's really good!
In Kyushu, tonkotsu ramen is the mainstream
but it's not like that in Tokyo
But in Tokyo, it's not like that.
I don't think there are many tonkotsu ramen restaurants in Tokyo.If you ask me, I don't think there are many tonkotsu ramen restaurants in Tokyo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kira's additional delivery was
Tapioca!
What?
We need some cream. No?
No, I think it's the size of the straw.
Is something wrong? Look.
Is that right? Is that the right size straw?
That's all I need to know.
Milk tea. Milk tea with whipped cream on top.
I just really need you to tell me the right straw.
Look.
I've never seen anything like it.
So the last of the food has arrived from Claire.
It smells like pizza.
It smells like pizza when it arrives!
It's rice.
It was chicken!
I'm so happy!
It's a surprisingly strong vegetable.
Isn't it very healthy?
You get your vegetables.
Get some protein.
And rice.
It's healthy.
And it's absolutely delicious!
I can't believe you got a big chicken like this.
I need chopsticks.
Oh, yeah.
Spicy!
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
You just said "sakoo" so loudly!
I wonder if it's okay to be so happy.
I don't know if there's any other way to describe it except that it's delicious.
It's really too delicious.
Seriously, everyone in the world
should make eating good food a hobby!
Yes, I'm a little surprised.
Just now, Claire suddenly said to me...
Um, another one arrived.
She asked me to look outside the door.
So I looked.
And then...
Oh my God, are those waffles?
I'm so happy!
And they're strawberry, my favorite.
Claire, what's going on?
She said it was a surprise.
I'm so happy.
Bon appétit!
I've never had them before.
I don't know how to eat it.
Mmm...
Mmm.
It's great.
Is that it? It's like a waffle version of crepe batter.
Hmm? I don't know. I don't know where I found it.
Thanks, Claire. Bye bye.
So, dinner arrived from Momoka!
What is it? It's scary. But I can see it's some kind of bread.
Bread. Wow! This looks delicious.
Bread and what is this, meat? Meat.
And there are two of the same thing. It's not a mistake.
This one and this one are the same.
The same one and the other one...
Bread.
Eh...
What is it?
Dinner.
But I'm glad. This meat looks delicious.
Bon appétit!
I'll have some.
Is it a thigh?
It's so good!
Mmm! Mochi Mochi!
Mmm! Meat and bread go well together!
For dinnerDinner.
Chicken lunch box
And bread!
Amazing! Delicious!
I'm going to eat this
I'm going to eat it slowly!
Bye-bye!
Okay, so that's how we did it,
Anything you want to say?
Well, I think it's a bit much to send us a fresh cucumber.
No, because you have to think about nutrition. There was no greenery at all, that's why I sent it to you.
You sent it to me in two batches. And I was hoping that Kira would send me tapioca or something.
The UBER guy was really weird about it when I handed it over.
What? I was like, "What's this?" I thought, "It's long and thin, and it's like a cucumber.
But the UBER guy was the most confused. I wanted to see that. Really? It was so embarrassing to receive it.
Where did you order the cucumber?
Some supermarket. Oh, a supermarket?
Oh, you know, Normal Stone.
I think. They bring them to me.
But, you know, I was really looking for tapioca. But, uh, I'm going UBER.
Hey. It's the same time.
How much is it if I order a cucumber UBER?
About 700 yen.
I bet you could buy tapioca for that.
I feel like I could have asked for something better.
I think I could have asked for something better, but I think I could have asked for something better.
I delivered waffles to Momochan.
Momochan, you know, she sent me a lot of requests.
You know, she said so.
I wondered why the person who asked for these things asked for them without permission, and then received them.
But I answered her request. I did.
You're so kind.
But I want ~.
Ah, I don't like ~.
Oh, Kira is here, too.
〜I don't like ~ and ~.
Dislike food.
But I, myself, ate something a little strange.
Let me try that too,
That was fun.
So, are you all right now?
I'm fine.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
Well, I hope we can do it again.
Okay, thank you very much for watching.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button, leave a comment, or subscribe to our channel.
Bye bye.